Guide to the Afro-American Cultural Center at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Digitized photographs of individuals, activities and events [computer files], Circa 1960s-1990s; Accession 2005-A-190
  - Kelly Desouza, Shelly Long, Jometric, Mike Morgan, Theresa Thornton, Katrina Clarke [00426.tif], 1985; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kimberly Scott, YSD, cast of Joe Turner [00427.tif], 1986; computer file (TIFF)
  - l-r Dean Howard Lamar, Jeanne C. Davis [AACC board], Harry Woyes, Career Services Director, House Reception [00428.tif], 1983 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Liese Klein, Benno Inauguration [00429.tif], 1986 September 20; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lisa Little [Grant Little's sister] [00430.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Manning Marable [00431.tif-00437.tif], 1987 March; 7 computer files (TIFF)
  - Mariam Makeba, Hugh Masekela Concert [00438.tif-00454.tif], 1988; 17 computer files (TIFF)
  - Mitty Owens [00455.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Nzinga dancers [00456.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - One Woman Show on Alice Walker, Drama Student [00457.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Patricia Romney and Caroline Jackson, l-r [00458.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Pearlena Igbokwe [00459.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Pearlena Igbokwe 1987 [r], Sheila Ducksworth 1989, Judy Oriole 1989, Terry Edwards 1989 [00460.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Pearlena Igbokwe 1987, Emily Reeves, Jackie, no date, Emily Hooper 1988, Judy Oriole 1989, Kim Barker 1989, Beth Coleman 1988 [00461.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Ricky Ewing no.42 [00462.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Rosanne Adderly 1989 [00463.tif], 1987 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Shades [00464.tif-00465.tif], 1980s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Sonia Butler 1980, far left [00466.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - the house [00467.tif-00468.tif], 1980s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Theresa Thornton, Elizabeth Welcome, Katrina Clarke [00469.tif], 1985; computer file (TIFF)
  - Ian Striker [00470.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Well wishers to the class of 1985 [00471.tif-00473.tif], 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Wilbur Cross student Iris Blackmon views photo exhibit [00474.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Yale Gospel Choir, Black church anniversary [00475.tif], 1984-1985; computer file (TIFF)
  - YAMS Reception [00476.tif-00477.tif], 1987 March; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Charles Martin
    - Untitled [00478.tif-00479.tif], 1980s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Class of 1985 and others
    - Untitled [00480.tif-00493.tif], 1980s; 14 computer files (TIFF)
  - Film
    - Untitled [00494.tif-00535.tif], 1980s; 42 computer files (TIFF)
    - Untitled-545-Gloria Naylor [00536.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-546-Gloria Naylor [00537.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00538.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-548-Gloria Naylor [00539.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-549-Skip Gates [00540.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00541.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-551-Gloria Naylor [00542.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00543.tif-00578.tif], 1980s; 36 computer files (TIFF)
  - Heritage Theatre Ensemble-Slow Dance
    - Untitled [00579.tif-00586.tif], 1980s; 8 computer files (TIFF)
  - Photographic Illustrations, computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00587.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-115 [copyright] [00588.tif], 1980s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00589.tif-00590.tif], 1980s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00591.tif-00593.tif], 1980s; 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-077 [00594.tif], 1983 June; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00595.tif-00645.tif], 1980s; 51 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-153 [00646.tif], 1985 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-154 [00647.tif], 1985 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-155 [00648.tif], 1985 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-156 [00649.tif], 1986 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-157 [00650.tif], 1986 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-158 [00651.tif], 1985 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00652.tif-00658.tif], 1980s; 7 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-168 [00659.tif], 1985 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00660.tif-00662.tif], 1980s; 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-173 [00663.tif], 1983 March; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00664.tif-00674.tif], 1980s; 11
  - A Tribute to Malcolm X [00675.tif-00676.tif], 1990s; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - AACC annual picnic, James Gore, Marissa Gillian, Rasheed Meadows, Alisha, Anna [00677.tif], 1992; computer file (TIFF)
  - Amiri Baraka [second from right] [00678.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Bernice Cosey-Pulley [00679.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Dramatic Interpretations [00680.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Cornell Scott [00681.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Craig Foster [second from right] [00682.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Spike Lee [00683.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Desiree Pedesdeaux-Andrews, Dwight Andrews [00684.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Don Martin [track coach], Craig Foster, Ralph Dawson [00685.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Doris B. Randall at dinner [00686.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Doris B. Randall [00687.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Dorothy Height at dinner [00688.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Elise Wright, Clark Thompson [00689.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Elizabeth Martin, Linda Long, Cherlynn Pope, Mona Gerdes [00690.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Fabienne Moore, Melissa Pressley [00691.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - George West
    - Dr. Betty Shabazz, Alex Haley, Dr. Henrik CLarke, Titus Walker at Malcolm X conference [00692.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
    - Titus Walker and Alex Haley [00693.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Gerald Jaynes and another panelist [00694.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Gerald Jaynes and two other panelists [00695.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Gerald Jaynes [00696.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - James Thomas, Richard Levin [00697.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Jerry Streets, Michael Thompson, Richard Brodhead [00698.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Jerry Streets [00699.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - John Blassingame [00700.tif], 1990 November; computer file (TIFF)
  - Joya Jillis SY1994, Aliya Pitchford SM1994, open house [00701.tif], 1992 September; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kimberly Goff-Crews [credit Michael Marsland of Office of Public Affairs] [00702.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Kimberly Goff-Crews [Yale University Office of Public Information] [00703.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Larry Ferrell [00704.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Leon Wynter, Juanita Merchant [00705.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Lisa Fortuna [00706.tif], 1990 November; computer file (TIFF)
  - Maitreyi Mazumdar and another panelist [00707.tif-00709.tif], 1990 November; 3 computer files (TIFF)
  - Maitreyi Mazumdar [00710.tif], 1990 November; computer file (TIFF)
  - Margaret Mitchell, James Thoms, Richard Levin, Richard Brodhead [00711.tif], undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Mel Wilbourne [center] [00712.tif], undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Melba Johnson, Jesse Rhines, Mel Wilbourne, Jean Sinders, Ian Straker [00713.tif], undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Melba Lee, Diane Turner [00714.tif], undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Michael Thompson [left] [00715.tif], undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Namu Lwanga- Storyteller [00716.tif], undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Paul Gilroy [00718.tif-00719.tif], 1990 November; 2 computer files (TIFF)
  - r-l, Jerry Streets, Richard Brodhead [00720.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Raymond Diamond [00721.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Richard Brodhead [00722.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Richard Levin, Richard Brodhead [00723.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Richard Levin [00724.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Robert Farris Thompson [00725.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00726.tif-00759.tif], 1990s; 34 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-224 [00760.tif], 1998 March 28; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00761.tif-00789.tif], 1990s; 29 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-257 [00790.tif], 1998 March 28; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00791.tif-00814.tif], 1990s; 23 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-283 [00815.tif], 1993; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00816.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-285 [00817.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-286 [00818.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-287 [00819.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-288 [00820.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-289 [00821.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-290 [00822.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-291 [00823.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-292 [00824.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-293 [00825.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-294 [00826.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00827.tif-00830.tif], 1990s; 4 computer files (TIFF)
  - Untitled-299 [00831.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-300 [00832.tif], 1994 April; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00833.tif], 1990s; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled-302 [00834.tif], 1998 March 28; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [00835.tif-00866.tif], 1990s; 32 computer files (TIFF)
  - Film
    - Seniors 1984 [00867.tif-00908.tif], 42 computer files (TIFF)
    - Untitled-545-Gloria Naylor [00909.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-546-Gloria Naylor [00910.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00911.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-548-Gloria Naylor [00912.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-549-Skip Gates [00913.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00914.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-551-Gloria Naylor [00915.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00916.tif-00963.tif], Undated; 48 computer files (TIFF)
    - Untitled-615-Bill Anderson [00964.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-616-Bill Anderson [00965.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-617-Bill Anderson [00966.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00967.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-619- Walter Rodney [00968.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-620- Khalid Lum, Bill Anderson [00969.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-621-Walter Rodney [00970.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [00971.tif-00977.tif], Undated; 7 computer files (TIFF)
  - Monique
    - Charles Dutton [00978.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Class of 1980 [00979.tif], computer file (TIFF)
    - Khalid and students laughing on the steps [00980.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Patricia Romney and Caroline Jackson, l-r [00981.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Paul Huggins- Kike Ese Drummer [00982.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Shades [00983.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Staff Marvin Blakely, Niyomu Payton, no date, uknown, no date, Donna Dinkins, Sonia Butler, no date, no date, Ken Penn, Ian Streaker, Phoebe Tree [00984.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Stokely Carmichael [00985.tif], 1978; computer file (TIFF)
    - No date woman and Khalid Lum in front of Center [00986.tif], 1977 August; computer file (TIFF)
  - Glenn DeChabert
    - On vacation [00987.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Outside [00988.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Slides
    - Untitled [00989.tif-01179.tif], Undated; 195
  - Annual picnic [01180.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Calhoun Dining Hall [01181.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Sterling 3rd Floor East Asian Reading Room [01182.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Sweet Saturday night [01183.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Untitled [01184.tif-01191.tif], Undated; 7 computer files (TIFF)
  - Urban Improvement Corps
    - Adrienne Demand from Sheridan Middle School and tutor Alondra Cole 1980 [01192.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - John 1978 tutoring student [01193.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Tash Freeman [01194.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Tony Coleman from MLK school with tutor Keith St. John 1979 [01195.tif], Undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [01196.tif-01265.tif], Undated; 69 computer files (TIFF)
    - Untitled-374 [01266.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-375 [01267.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-376 [01268.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-377 [01269.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-378 [01270.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-379 [01271.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled-380 [01272.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [01273.tif-01276.tif], 4 computer files (TIFF)
    - Unititled-385 [01277.tif], 1993 October; computer file (TIFF)
    - Untitled [01277.tif-01396.tif], 119 computer files (TIFF)
- Digitized photographs of individuals, activities and events collected by Eugene Stuart, circa 1974-1979; Accession 2005-A-198
  - Standing: Roslyn Wilcots '76;Sitting[left to right]: Stuart Parker '75, Barbara Pickens '76, Bernette Mosley '74;Photographer: Gene Stuart;Location: Trumbull Common Room [190114e1.jpg], 1974 or 1975; computer file (JPEG)
  - [Left to right]: Joana [maybe], Jules nee George Jones '74, Keith Kishiyama '74;Photographer: Gene Stuart; Location: Trumbull Dining Hall [190114f0.jpg], computer file (JPEG)
  - Ray Diamond '73; Law '76, Brenda Stewart, Law '79;Photographer: Gene Stuart; Location: Cross-Campus during, 1976; computer file (JPEG)
  - Warren Smith '74; Photographer: Gene Stuart; Location: Trumbull Dining Hall [1901151f.jpg], 1973 -1974; computer file (JPEG)
  - [Left to right]: unknown, Frank Gaines '75; Photographer: Gene Stuart; Location: Trumbull Common room, 1974 - 1975; computer file (JPEG)
  - [Left to right]: John Wong '75, Eugene Stuart '76; Location: Trumbull College [1901153f.jpg], 1975; computer file (JPEG)
  - [Left to right]: Darryl Nash '76, Barbara Pickens, '76; Photographer: Brian Stuart; Location, Trumbull College, main courtyard [1901157d.jpg], 1976; computer file (JPEG)
  - [On the far right]: Arlette Bunch '77, Bruce McKenna '76; Photographer: Gene Stuart, computer file (JPEG)
  - Rollin Chippey '76 [from Davenport]; Photographer: Brian Stuart, 1976; computer file (JPEG)
  - [On right]: Roslyn Wilcots '76; Photographer: Brian Stuart; Location: Trumbull College, 1976; computer file (JPEG)
  - [Left to right [two in the middle in blue] Robert Fogelin, Master of Trumbull College, [carrying Trumbull College flag] Eugene Stuart '76; Photographer: Brian Stuart; Location: graduation procession on New Haven Green on way to the Old Campus [1901158d.jpg], 1976; computer file (JPEG)
  - Eugene Stuart '76 [holding Trumbull Flag before graduation procession to Old Campus]; Photographer: Elizabeth Goins; Location: Trumbull Courtyard [1901159c.jpg], 1976; computer file (JPEG)
- Records documenting the Afro-American Cultural Center Oral History Project and exhibit, circa 1968-2004; Accession 2006-A-072
  - Afro-American Cultural Center Bulletin, 1980 February (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Literate Soul, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Living Memory History Project, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Oral History Project, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "A proposal for a major in Afro-American Studies…" [photocopy], circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Photographs, posters, citation [oversize] (Box 2, Folder 8 - 11)
- Afro-American Cultural Center records, 1967-2006; Accession 2006-A-225
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2042
  - Directors
  - Police harassment, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence on house activities [Lum], 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 3)
  - Correspondence on activities [Lum], 1976-1977, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Directors' job descriptions, 1987, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Eldridge Cleaver [Black H. Mon], 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Varied reports, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 15th anniversary report and correspondence [Jackson], 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, alumni 15th anniversary, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Position of AACC, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence [Wade], 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - PROP
  - Participant evaluation [Goff-Crews], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Program [Sample Applications], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - HHMI -STARS annual report, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation of STARS Program, 1993, 1994, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence [Goff-Crews], 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Mellon Foundation Project, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - STARS Winners, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence [Aug.-Oct.] [Pamela Y. George], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Yale College Dean [Minutes] [George], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence [Nov. and Dec.], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Harry Truman Scholarships, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Davenport Fellowship [George], 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - STARS Correspondence [George], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Leadership Development for AACC, 200? (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - End of Year Report [George], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Financial Proposals, Plans, Reports [George], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Yale Police Dept., Licenses and Correspondence, 1990, 1991, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report [George], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Black History Month [George], 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Nikki Giovanni, 1999, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Beckman Scholars Program, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - STARS Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Prof. John Blassingame Memorial, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, MLK as Yale Official Holiday, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - STARS
  - Winners -Scholars, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Scholars program reports, 1996, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Program evaluation report, 2000-2001? (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Program release forms, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Letters of acceptance, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Ethnic counselors and counselees lists, letters, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence on African American faculty, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Outstanding achievement awards [Nominations], 2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Mellon-Bouchet fellows list, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - STARS correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - AACC development plan, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Yale College Organizational Development, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Achievement awards nominees, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Beckman Scholars program correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - STARS Scholars program [sample] applications, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence
  - Miscellaneous, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Thank you notes, Varied dates (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Thank you cards, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Thank you letters, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Ethnic counselor program, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Student recommendations, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Annual report, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence on Bianca Jones, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Black Achievement Awards, 1996-1998, 2000, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ethnic Counselor program - varied, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 35th Anniversary Planning, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Winners AACC Outstanding Awards, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 63 - 64)
  - Board of directors
  - Report, Black Reaction to…; Letter to Brewester, 1973, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Long range plan, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Management and fiscal plan, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Minutes, correspondence, 1980-1981, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Minutes, correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Junior board, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Lists, agendas, minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bylaws, 1982, 1997, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Agendas, minutes, 1998-2004 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Administration and finance
  - Proposal for operation budget, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Letter from President Benno Schmidt, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Sheila Saunders, administrative assistant, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Pachanga correspondence, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Sample fiscal summaries, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Maintenance contracts, 1996-1999, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - House Staff, job descriptions, 200? (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - 1996-1997 AACC Report, student adv. committee, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - House Staff, agendas and minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Kente Cloth receipts (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Sample staff job applications, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Sample financial statements, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Marsh insurance, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Speakers contracts [Sonia Sanchez, Hon. Walter Fauntroy], 2001 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Yale Police Dept. invoices [sample], 1996-1999, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Sample AACC budget, Nov and Dec, 2002-03 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - House staff, plans for AACC archives, 2003, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - House staff lists, wage correspondence, 1984, 2001-2005 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Yale-Harvard Weekend -DJs contracts, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Resident groups
  - Guidelines, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Meeting minutes, 1996-2005 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha fraternity, Inc., 1988, 1996, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha sorority, Inc., 1993-2005 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Black Church at Yale, 1994-2004 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Black Graduate Network, 1990-2005 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1973-2005 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, Inc., 1993-2006 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Ethnic Performers Guild at Yale, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Gamma Phi Delta Christian fraternity, Inc., 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Heritage Theater ensemble, 1980-2006 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi fraternity, Inc, 1988-2004 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi fraternity, Inc [Hazing Issues], 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Konjo!, 2002, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - National Society of Black Engineers, 1996-2006 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Pan, Jam and Lime Steel Orchestra, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Omega Psi Phi fraternity, Inc., 1993-1994, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Pre-Health African American and Latino students, 1996, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Prism, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Shades, 1993-1994, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Sphere, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Steppin' Out, 1999-2006 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Urban Improvement Corps [UIC], 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - UIC, 1998-2006 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - UIC financial documents, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Visions of Virtue, 2003-2006 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Yale African Students Association [YASA], 1993-1994, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - YASA, IASA Conference Bid, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Yale Gospel Choir, 1994-2006 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Yale West Indian Student Org./Caribbean Club, 1993-2006 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Adam, Eve and Steve Productions, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Akili, undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - ALAAFIA, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Agape Bible and Prayer Fellowship, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 129)